and today is day three.
this is maia.
maya is a brazilian
who has lived in Mozambique for fifteen years.
was a missionary,
tv director,
let's just say she's the most unrolled person here.
if maia can help me,
I'm done.
now it's good,
old man.
good morning,
good morning!
I'm going to publicize the show,
is nice.
a
person who shows more talent,
I'll give a check myself.
was already inside to enter the program
then it gave a tummy ache.
welcome,
what do you call the program
happy live mornings.
is
a great pleasure to meet you and be here.
with you today,
thank you,
thank you.
tomorrow,
ten o'clock in the morning,
mafalá bell.
man,
now there's no way,
bro,
it's tomorrow,
Brother.
now is to hope that it works,
have people there,
hope everything goes well.
Is it on?
until tomorrow.